const QuestionOne = {
    Question:"Which is the correct method to define a block element as a grid?",
    Answer:"display: grid;",
    A1:"None of these",
    A2:"grid: true;",
    A3:"show: grid;",
    A4:"display: grid;"
}
const QuestionTwo = {
    Question:"What is the correct syntax for a CSS comment",
    Answer:"/* Comment Goes Here */",
    A1:"'Comment Goes Here'",
    A2:"# Comment Goes Here #",
    A3:"// Comment Goes Here",
    A4:"/* Comment Goes Here */"
}
const QuestionThree = {
    Question:"Which CSS style position an element relative to the browser window?",
    Answer:"position: fixed;",
    A1:"position: absolute;",
    A2:"position: relative;",
    A3:"position: static;",
    A4:"position: fixed;"
}
const QuestionFour = {
    Question:"What is the main purpose of CSS in the HTML5",
    Answer:"CSS is used to determine style, positioning, and layout of a page.",
    A1:"CSS is used to define content on a page.",
    A2:"CSS is used for scripting on an HTML web Page.",
    A3:"None of these",
    A4:"CSS is used to determine style, positioning, and layout of a page."
}
const QuestionFive = {
    Question:"Which box model establishes content alignment, direct and orientation?",
    Answer:"Flexible Box Model",
    A1:"Parent Box Model",
    A2:"Flexible Box Model",
    A3:"Inheritance Box Model",
    A4:"Fixed Box Model"
}
const QuestionSix = {
    Question:"How does the new Flexible Box Model eliminate the need for using float?",
    Answer:"By providing a container positioned by properties assigned",
    A1:"By positioning objects relative to a parent object",
    A2:"By positioning all objects at the coordinates 0,0",
    A3:"By allowing the browser to position the objects",
    A4:"By providing a container positioned by properties assigned"
}
const QuestionSeven = {
    Question:"Which is true about absolute positioning?",
    Answer:"The element is positioned relative to the upper-left corner of the browser",
    A1:"The element is positioned relative to the upper-left corner of the computer display window",
    A2:"The element can float right or left",
    A3:"The element is positioned relative to the upper-left corner of the browser",
    A4:"The element is positioned relative to its parent element"
}
const QuestionEight = {
    Question:"How to create a CSS style what changes the color of the text?",
    Answer:".identifier { color: rgba(0,0,255, 0.40); }",
    A1:".identifier { font-color: #0000ff, 60%; }",
    A2:".identifier { text-color: rgba(0%,0%,100%,40%); }",
    A3:".identifier { color: rgba(0,0,255, 0.40); }",
    A4:".identifier { background-color: rgba(0,0,255,60); }"
}
const QuestionNine = {
    Question:"The CSS _____ properties are used to create space around elements, outside of any defined borders.",
    Answer:"margin",
    A1:"padding",
    A2:"margin",
    A3:"box-spacing",
    A4:"box-space"
}
const QuestionTen = {
    Question:"With the CSS _____ property you can do 3D transformation.",
    Answer:"transform",
    A1:"3d-move",
    A2:"transform",
    A3:"move(x,y,z)",
    A4:"z-property"
}